

DMYTRO RIABTSUN

Phone: 063 217-41-91

E-mail: riabtsun@i.ua

LinkedIn / riabtsun

Website: riabtsun.github.io/portfolio

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hi, my name is Dmytro, and I'm learning front-end development So far, I'm interested in all that will help to better master this profession. Stubborn and motivated to develop my skills and abilities to grow professionally. I love turning layouts into websites. I have theoretical and practical experience in the front-end that is necessary for a successful start in this position.

In my free time I like to play with friends in a band, or spend time on walks.

EXPERIENCE

SALES MANAGER

Trading house Sodruzhestvo (2020 - present)

- · Attraction of new clients
- · making sales

PUBLIC RELATIONS INSPECTOR

Patrol Police Department in Dnipropetrovsk region (2015 - 2020)

- Community policing
- Work with the media
- · Scientific and educational activities

SKILLS

- Javascript
- Basic knowledge about jquery
- Basic knowledge about git
- HTML/CSS
- SASS
- Bootstrap
- Figma/Avacode

LANGUAGES

• English - intermediate

EDUCATION

GRADUATE

Hillel it school, Dnipro (2020-2021)

- Front-End Basic, Exellent grade
- Front-End Pro, Exellent grade

LAWYER

Dnipropetrovsk State University of Internal Affairs (2010 - 2008)